Contact

maeggers9@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/maegan-komp-a73979108 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Basic Life Support (BLS)
Patient Safety
Healthcare

Maegan Komp

Travel Nurse at LRS Healthcare

Fort Smith, Arkansas Area

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Hospitals, Healthcare Management, Healthcare, Basic Life Support (BLS), and Patient Safety. Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor of Science - BS focused in Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse from Arkansas Tech University.

Experience

LRS Healthcare
Travel Nurse
July 2019 - Present (1 year 1 month)

Washington Regional Medical Center RN June 2017 - January 2020 (2 years 8 months) Fayetteville, Arkansas

PRN surgical periop area

Skyline Med Staff, LLC preop/pacu travel nursing September 2018 - March 2019 (7 months)

Catholic medical center - Manchester, NH December 31,2018- March 30,2019.

Methodist medical center - Oakridge TN Sept 4,2018 - Dec 2,2018. Pacu / recovery RN.

Sparks Health System
Staff RN
July 2017 - August 2018 (1 year 2 months)
Fort Smith, Arkansas

Preop RN in ambulatory surgery center

Page 1 of 2

Mercy Staff RN October 2016 - March 2018 (1 year 6 months) Fort Smith, Arkansas Area

Conway Regional Medical Center Staff RN May 2015 - October 2016 (1 year 6 months)

Education

Arkansas Tech University

Bachelor of Science - BS, Registered Nursing/Registered

Nurse · (2010 - 2014)